<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yifei Liu</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yifei Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyze U.S. Census Data using Tidycensus</title>
      <link>/blog/analyze-u-s-census-data-using-tidycensus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/analyze-u-s-census-data-using-tidycensus/</guid>
      <description>Just fininsh Tidycensus class on Datacamp which is called Analyzing US Census Data in R so I think it will will a great opportunity for me to practice my data visualization skills.
Show Pennsylvania Median Income You need to obtain a API code from U.S. Census and set it up in .Rprofile.
library(tidyverse) library(tidycensus) library(ggplot2) library(purrr) library(shiny) library(viridis) library(sf) library(plotly) # devtools::install_github(&amp;#39;thomasp85/gganimate&amp;#39;) library(gganimate) # census_api_key(key = &amp;quot;Your API Keys&amp;quot;) library(ggthemes) library(mapview) Next we need to find median income data, you can use load_variables function to find the variables name that you want to find, you can also use Census Reporter to browser different categories of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A small project example : add yours !</title>
      <link>/projects/small-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/small-project/</guid>
      <description>Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.
 He rather enjoys tea, but seems to have trouble obtaining it in the far reaches of the galaxy.
 In time, he learns how to fly and carves a niche for himself as a sandwich-maker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Yifei Liu. I&amp;rsquo;m interest in Data Visulation, Government, Financial Engineer, anime, and R.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently a student at Temple Universtiy Fox School major in Financial Analyst and Risk Management. I will graduate in 2019.
I current live in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>In this theme, it is possible to add sections like a Projects one for example. You can add plenty of articles about your projects and a presentation page that will be displayed before the list. All is modulable, if you don&amp;rsquo;t want something.
A Hollywood-funded film version, produced and filmed in the UK, was released in April 2005, and radio adaptations of the third, fourth, and fifth novels were broadcast from 2004 to 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>